<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Sport And Music</string>
    <string name="main_text">Choose activity:</string>
    <string name="gym">The list for gymnastics (or any other same dynamic sport, like walking, strengthening, etc.) is appear here in a list. If it\'s empty, you will have a message which ask you to add music from your library. You can reach your library with the list icon below. On the top you can navigate between the gym list\'s elements. The headphone icon will navigate you to the now playing section. You can find a timer icon -hour glass- here, which you can use when you want a HIIT or any other interval training. In this case a window will pop up, where the interval settings appear. After the settings, parallel with the music, the sound signs in the period the user set is coming.</string>
    <string name="run">The list for running (or any other fast sport, like aerobic, etc.) is appear here in a list. If it\'s empty, you will have a message which ask you to add music from your library. You can reach your library with the list icon below. On the top you can navigate between the run list\'s elements. The headphone icon will navigate you to the now playing section. You can find a timer icon -hour glass- here, which you can use when you want a HIIT or any other interval training. In this case a window will pop up, where the interval settings appear. After the settings, parallel with the music, the sound signs in the period the user set is coming.</string>
    <string name="yoga">The list for yoga (or any other slow sport, like stretching or relaxing etc.) is appear here in a list. If it\'s empty, you will have a message which ask you to add music from your library. You can reach your library with the list icon below. On the top you can navigate between the yoga list\'s elements. The headphone icon will navigate you to the now playing section. You can find a timer icon -hour glass- here, which you can use when you want a HIIT or any other interval training. In this case a window will pop up, where the interval settings appear. After the settings, parallel with the music, the sound signs in the period the user set is coming.</string>
    <string name="now_playing">The musicplayer section. This is where the musics are played. The currently played music\'s every detail (title, artist, style, lenght) are appear here in a card view. With the + button above you can add the musics to different sport activities you want. With the settings icon you can reach sound settings like equaliser, pitch and speed in a popup window. \n The home button below navigate the user to the app\'s main screen, the list icon to the library.</string>
    <string name="list">Data of music and the music itself arrives from online database such as Spotify API or from the device itself. From this listview short press on music you can open the now playing screen, or with long press you can add the music to the chosen sport list. \nThe home button below navigate the user to the app\'s main screen,the headphone to the now playing screen.</string>
    <string name="main">This is the main screen of the app. In this application you can create playlists to different intensity sports. With the pictograms above you can choose your current activity\'s intensity, and the music will start. \nThe buttons below are navigate to the library, and the headphone icon navigate to the now playing section. You can add new songs to the lists from both.</string>
</resources>
